Um... maybe...
I should take a shower first.
Getting cold feet after coming this far?
That's not...
You're trying to act calm and cool,
but I can tell.
You can tell what?
Why not just say...
it's your first time?
That's not...
true.
Are you… sure?
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
My heart's racing.
Is this love?
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 1]
Go Ai!
Hey, Reo! What was that?
You got sloppy at the end, Aiko.
Just because you're a little taller than me?
It's more about skill level than height.
Let's go another round!
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
I'm not gonna lose next time!
You sure keep fighting after losing, every time.
If I beat him,
I'll be the best player in the basketball club.
You two sure are great rivals, huh?
That's because Reo is my enemy.
[AIKO KASUMI: an energetic, competitive, basketball-loving high school girl]
You're totally messing around with that Aiko Kasumi, right?
Well, she's funny.
She gets worked up so quickly and then challenges me to a game.
[REO AMANO: the most popular guy at Kafuu High School and the ace of the basketball club]
So you really do enjoy it, after all.
[KENJI KUBO: Reo's best friend and basketball teammate since middle school]
Well, she is my toy.
Next time, I'm, definitely, not going to lose!
[Kasumi]
Yum! Meat is the best!
[RANJI KASUMI: the easily-flattered third son, often swayed by his girlfriend]
Aiko, you jerk...
That meat was mine! Aiko!
Pipe down!
Crap. I'm going to be sick.
Your meat is my meat, and my meat is my meat!
- Aiko!
- What, what?
Wait, Aiko!
Drank too much, Ritsuki?
My meat!
[MAKOTO KASUMI: first son and parental substitute when the parents are gone]
That's too much meat talk for one morning.
- Oh, right. Dad and Mom said they're in Paris now.
- Really?
Makoto, stop eating and catch her!
Here you go. Have a good day!
- Thank you, dear brother!
- Aiko, this isn't over—
Victory is mine. See you later!
Ranji, isn't it time you stop bickering so wildly with our little sister?
She's never acted like a little sister!
[Kafuu High School]
Wait, wait, wait!
What do you want so early in the morning?
Let's go another round, Reo.
I won't lose today!
- What is it?
- Well...
- Thanks for the morning chuckle.
- Huh?
Is that a yes or no?
I accept your challenge.
Yes!
[Kafuu High School]
I lost.
I win.
- Ai!
- She's so cool!
Ai, I'll always be devoted to you!
[ERENA YAMAGUCHI: the leader of Ai's groupies]
I appreciate it. I may lose the games,
but when it comes to number of fans, I win.
One, two...
Eight?!
Seven!
So I win?
That jerk! With his smug little face...
Reo's super popular.
Everyone's got lovey-dovey eyes for him.
He's just a tiny bit better than me at basketball!
Yeah. And he's handsome and gets great grades.
I hate it. He's so perfect, it makes me sick!
You haven't changed a bit since third grade, Ai.
Even though everyone is nuts about boyfriends and having sex...
you're all, "Basketball! Game! God damn it!"
It's endearing, but I do worry.
[HIROKO KITAUCHI: Ai's best friend since childhood. Very understanding.]
What? Worry? About what?
You're a high school girl that knows nothing about love.
I don't care about that!
Basketball is a hundred times more fun than love!
What are you doing?!
The wind of love is 100 times sweeter!
Love sweeps through our entire body. It makes you feel like your heart is about to stop.
What's wrong, Hiroko? You're acting weird today.
I'm about to be bowled over by a gust of wind.
Does that mean you're...?
- In love.
- In love?!
Will you help me?
If that's the case, just leave it to me!
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
I'm sorry. I don't think I can do this.
Three of the girls quit all at once, so it's been hard.
Didn't you know that Ritsuki's been having trouble?
He's just reaping what he's sown.
But if I'm seen wearing this, my life is over!
Yeah, it's over. My cafe is over, too!
[RITSUKI KASUMI: Second son, manager of the maid cafe, lady-killer playboy]
Turning someone with no sex appeal to anyone into a maid...
Hey, Ritsuki! I can hear everything you say.
Don't you think that's rude to say to your little sister?
Oh, sorry! So you're my little sister, huh? Not brother?
Screw him. I hope this cafe goes under, and he becomes homeless forever.
Come on now, both of you.
What's so great about Ritsuki, anyway?
He's the most perverted, idiotic loser of all my brothers!
That's kind of cute about him.
It's like you can't leave him on his own.
No way.
Ritsuki!
What's up with this place? There's no one here.
Welcome home, Master.
- I'm very sorry, we're still getting ready—
- There's a sign outside, ain't there?!
"Post-Refurbishment Reopening," it says.
I told you, I'm not being a maid!
- So you're going to lose this game?
- Huh?
This is a battleground between men and women.
Who will seize the initiative?
How much can you enthrall the guy?
If you forfeit the game and run away, you lose.
I lose?
This is your weapon. Might be too difficult for you, though.
So please, Master, if you'd wait a little longer...
I've had enough of this!
Master! What's the matter?
You're so cute!
Master! You're leaving already?
I'd like an extension!
Thank you very much!
I hope you'll eat lots and regain your strength!
- One of everything!
- Yay!
Thank you very much!
Cocoa drink, full of energy... Shoot!
- It's a goal, a goal!
- A goal!
- Enjoy!
- Thank you!
She's got a knack for it.
But you're cuter, Hiroko.
No way.
Have a good night!
- See you!
- Please come again!
I'll be waiting!
This might actually be really fun!
Welcome!
No way!
Welcome home!
- Huh? Kitauchi?
- That's right.
[DAICHI & RYOTA: 2nd year students at Kafuu High, members of the basketball club]
- You work here?
- I do.
You're such a cute maid!
What are you guys doing here all together?
- We got a coupon from over there.
- I see! Well, I'll show you to a seat.
Over there. Three meters. Straight ahead.
Right, right. Over there.
Come on, I'll show you!
So? What do you want to eat? Pick from here.
Hey...
I'm sorry!
- I'm really sorry!
- It's okay.
What do I do? It's not coming out!
- Hey...
- I apologize!
I'll pay for the dry cleaning!
You're...
cute.
Don't worry about the cleaning.
Tell me your name.
I'm Reo Amano.
What's your name?
My name...
Mai Toda? Who's that?
It's my grandma's name. Mai Toda.
- Oh! The one that rode around on that huge motorcycle?
- Yeah.
Reo was totally enthralled by the college student Mai Toda.
He had no idea it was me.
Look.
[Mai, please go on a date with me.]
No one realized it was you.
Right?
And Reo invited me out!
- As soon as he falls in love with me, ta-da!
- No, no!
And so I'll be counting on you!
Huh? Counting on me for what?
You'll lend me some super cute clothes, right?
Sure, I guess that's fine.
Reo's a guy, though. If things turn serious, he might do something rash.
Bring it on! If he takes it seriously, I win.
Then the game ends.
It's so pretty.
This is an amazing little hidden place!
I came here a lot with my family as a kid.
- The sunset is really pretty here.
- The sand feels great!
Are you listening to what I'm saying?
Come on! Get over here, Reo!
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
♫ You are so free ♫
♫ You are suspicion ♫
♫ Been a lonely, lonely, lonely, lonely only ♫
♫ Lonely, lonely, lonely, lonely only ♫
I wish we had brought some swimsuits.
The water's too cold for swimming now.
I'd be fine!
I see something! It's a tiny fish!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you just dizzy?
Or are you trying to tempt me?
What?
Oh! No, that's not...
Let's head back.
I'll buy you a change of clothes from somewhere.
Okay.
What? There are no more busses?
That's a little early!
The last bus just left.
We can take a taxi to the train station...
but will one drive by?
Why don't we walk?
The last train will be gone by the time we get there.
That's true.
But we'll catch a cold if we stay outdoors like this...
[Love Hotel]
Should we go...
take a rest?
That's fine.
Let's...
stay the night.
So this is a love hotel...
Mai.
Thank you.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
I see.
You're...
used to this, aren't you?
You come to places like this a lot?
Would you like to find out?
What?
Mai...
Um... maybe...
I should take a shower first.
Getting cold feet after coming this far?
That's not...
You're trying to act calm and cool,
but I can tell.
You can tell what?
Why not just say…
it's your first time?
That's not...
true.
Are you...
sure?
I'm sorry...
for making you nervous.
I wasn't that nervous…
You've been making my heart go nuts,
so I just wanted to change it up and make your heart beat faster.
What do you mean?
You don't know?
Anyway,
I don't want things with you to be half-hearted, Mai.
They have bathrobes,
so I'll go change first.
A hotel?!
[I'm staying the night in a hotel with Reo... Please be my alibi!]
I'm good for your alibi.
But don't rush into anything, okay?
I'm sorry. Were you waiting?
You look totally different from usual.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'll sleep on the sofa.
You use the bed.
No, that's way too small for you.
The bed is so big, we can both sleep there.
I can't do that.
I'm really holding myself back,
but I don't know what could happen in the bed.
We'll just... sleep quietly tonight.
Good night.
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
Mai...
are you okay?
Yeah.
♫ I don't wish for anyone to know my secret ♫
♫ I want to steal you away ♫
♫ The secret that belongs to only us. 1on1 ♫
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
♫ Only I know this ♫
This is a game.
♫ Rather than touching each other, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
A game I can either win or lose.
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
Well...
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
I'm really embarrassed,
so, let me come out and say it like this.
Please,
let's start dating, for real.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
So, this...
isn't love. Definitely not.
[Next time]
He's acting like nothing happened.
Then lock Aiko away!
That's love!
You've got to be kidding me. Someone like Reo?
You don't sit around and wait for destiny, you reach out and grab it.
I wasn't serious about it!
You said you lost, but you really won from the start.
[This drama is a work of fiction]